{
    "subject": "Y\u0131lmaz_G\u00fcney",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Yol",
    "human_readable": "Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney produced the film Yol.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9163879752159119,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8373575210571289,
            "question": "Who produced the film Yol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7804010510444641,
            "question": "Are there any other films produced by Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7010436058044434,
            "question": "Is Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6579886674880981,
            "question": "What year was the film Yol released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4976799786090851,
            "question": "Who were some of the actors in the film Yol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4155845046043396,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in the film Yol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.390319287776947,
            "question": "What genre is the film Yol likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37362438440322876,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the film Yol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34153127670288086,
            "question": "Has the film Yol won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney produced the film Yol.",
            "html": "yago_6535_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the film Yol?",
            "html": "yago_6535_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Yol likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_6535_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some themes explored in the film Yol?",
            "html": "yago_6535_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6535_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide information about Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney being a Kurdish film director, scenarist, novelist, and actor who produced movies in Turkish, including the film \"Yol\". The documents also mention that he co-produced the film \"Yol\" with \u015eerif G\u00f6ren, which implies that he was involved in producing the film. Therefore, the information supports the triple that Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney produced the film Yol."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney produced the film Yol.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention that Y\u0131lmaz G\u00fcney won the Palme d'Or with the film 'Yol', indicating his role in producing or co-producing the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}